{
    "subject": "Kay_Bennett",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Fox_Crane",
    "human_readable": "Kay Bennett is married to Fox Crane.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9865771532058716,
            "question": "Is there a marriage between Kay Bennett and Fox Crane?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9785632491111755,
            "question": "Does Kay Bennett have a husband named Fox Crane?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9560456275939941,
            "question": "Are Kay Bennett and Fox Crane a couple?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.866966187953949,
            "question": "To whom is Kay Bennett married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8588536977767944,
            "question": "Who is Kay Bennett married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7708593606948853,
            "question": "Who are Fox Crane and Kay Bennett related to each other?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6411982178688049,
            "question": "Is Kay Bennett in a relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6219707131385803,
            "question": "What is the name of Fox Crane's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6154518127441406,
            "question": "What is the marital status of Kay Bennett?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21988782286643982,
            "question": "Is Fox Crane single?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Kay Bennett is married to Fox Crane.",
            "html": "yago_30226_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the marital status of Kay Bennett?",
            "html": "yago_30226_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Fox Crane's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_30226_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Kay Bennett in a relationship?",
            "html": "yago_30226_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30226_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30226_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30226_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30226_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30226_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30226_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30226_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30226_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30226_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30226_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provided contain information about Kay and her relationships with other characters, including Fox Crane. The information indicates that Kay initially became engaged to Fox, but later left him when she learned he was not dying as he claimed. However, the documents also indicate that Kay eventually married Fox Crane in July 2008, after being with Miguel and having a daughter named Maria. Therefore, the triple \"Kay Bennett is married to Fox Crane\" is supported by the information in the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe provided context clearly states that \"Kay and Miguel were eventually married in July 2008,\" but more importantly, it also mentions, \"The two became engaged, but Kay came to regret this decision when an available and interested Miguel returned to Harmony. Kay married Fox because she believed that he was dying, but leaves him when she learns his illness is a sham.\" This information supports the triple stating that Kay Bennett is married to Fox Crane."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}